<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	    <title>Braintapper Blog</title>
	    <link>https://www.braintapper.com</link>
	    <description>Latest articles from the Braintapper Blog</description><item>
	<title>Basecamp's Guide To Internal Communication</title>
	<link>https://www.braintapper.com/blog/basecamps-guide-to-internal-communication</link>
	<description>Basecamp published their guide to internal communication recently, and it is insightful and excellent.
Some highlights:

Meetings are the last resort, not the first option.
...
If your words can be perceived in different ways, they&#39;ll be understood in the way which does the most harm.
...
&quot;Now&quot; is often the wrong time to say what just popped into your head. It&#39;s better to let it filter it through the sieve of time. What&#39;s left is the part worth saying.
...
Write at the...</description>
	<pubDate>Fri Jan 10 2020 12:04:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Check out my Articles</title>
	<link>https://www.braintapper.com/blog/check-out-my-articles-section</link>
	<description>As mentioned in my first post, I have an Articles section on the site where I&#39;ll be posting evergreen articles that will continue to be updated over time.
I have two articles in place now:

The Windows Software I use to Stay Productive - This is a list of software that I recommend for Windows users.
My Favorite Self-Hosted Applications - This is a list of mostly Docker containers (for now) that I recommend running in your own environment.

I have a queue of other useful articles on their...</description>
	<pubDate>Mon Jan 06 2020 12:02:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Convert an Outlook PST to JSON</title>
	<link>https://www.braintapper.com/blog/converting-an-outlook-pst-to-json</link>
	<description>I had to archive an Outlook mailbox to a PST file recently, but I&#39;m not a huge fan of using Outlook for finding e-mails.
I looked around for tools that would convert a PST to JSON so I could load my data into something like Postgresql, but I didn&#39;t
find anything that was free (I only need to do the conversion once).
I ended up searching for an NPM that could extract objects from a PST, and found epfromer&#39;s pst-extractor..
Using that NPM, I made a simple command line tool for Windows...</description>
	<pubDate>Mon Jan 06 2020 12:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>So I Wrote a Database Migrations NPM</title>
	<link>https://www.braintapper.com/blog/pg-forward-migrations</link>
	<description>I&#39;ve been working on making Docker containers of my personal Nodejs projects lately, and for those that rely on a relational database (namely Postgresql), I wanted to be able to run database migrations on them locally to make updates easier. To be clear, I&#39;m not talking about data migrations, which are a completely different thing.
For database migrations outside of Ruby on Rails, I&#39;ve been using Liquibase, and more recently, Flyway. They&#39;re both perfectly fine tools, but they...</description>
	<pubDate>Mon Dec 30 2019 12:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Welcome to the New Site</title>
	<link>https://www.braintapper.com/blog/welcome-to-the-new-site</link>
	<description>Well it&#39;s been a while since the site has been updated. A long while, actually.
It&#39;s been a long time coming, but I forced myself over the holidays to revamp the site, and here it is.
Things are going to be rough for a little while, as this is a work in progress, and I&#39;ve opted to go live with a buggy site as opposed to leaving a placeholder page up. This should force me to iterate more quickly and more often.
So before I rebuilt the site, I went through a lot of hand-wringing...</description>
	<pubDate>Sun Dec 29 2019 12:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>